graspskills.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | GraspSkills

  * Management courses
  * Agile courses
  * IT courses
  * Other courses

  1. [Home](http://www.graspskills.com/)
  2. Privacy Policy

#### Graspskills Training & Consulting: Web site Privacy Policy for <http://www.graspskills.com/>

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

#### To improve our website

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

#### To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

#### To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

#### To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

Our online payment facility through our payment gateway/s automatically encrypts your confidential information in transit from your computer to ours using the 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer protocol (SSL) for 100% safe, secure, confidential, and convenient online transaction.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Should we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified at 3:25pm IST on Thursday, September 12, 2013.
